President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of Abram Brubacher Records, 1904-1930; 2; 14.8
  - Alphabetic File - We, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Wh, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Wia - Wil, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Wo - Wy, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Wo - Wy, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Y, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Z, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - American Social Hygene Association, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Chamber of Commence, Albany, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - A, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Ba - Bl, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Bo - By, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Ca - Cl, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Co - Cy, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - D, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - E, 1922-1923 (Box 8 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - F, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - G, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Hal, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Hal, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Har - Hy, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - I - J, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Faculty Applications, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Graves, Frank P. Commision of Education, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Horner, Harlan, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Reciprocal Relation, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Sabbatical Year, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Speaking, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Staff Letters, Memorabilia, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - State Legislature, 1922-1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Appointment + Application, Professional, 1923 (Box 9 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Bertha Bandwell, 1923 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Commencement, 1923 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - English Dept., 1923 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - School of Citizenship, 1923 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Vocational Education, 1923 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Aa - Al, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Al - An, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Am - Ar, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - As - Ay, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - Baa - Bar, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Bar - Bas, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - Be - Bh, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - Bi - Bl, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Bo - By, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Bra - Bri, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - Bro - Bry, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Bu - By, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Ca - Cd, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Ce - Cl, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Coa - Con, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Coo- Coz, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Cr - Cu, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - Cu - Cy, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - Da - De, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Di - Do, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - Dr - Dy, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - Ea - En, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Eo - Ey, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Fa - Fi, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - Fi - Fo, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - Fr - Fy, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Alphabetic File - Ga - Ge, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Alphabetic File - Gi - Gi, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Alphabetic File - Gr - Gy, 1923-1924 (Box 10 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Alphabetic File - Ha - Han, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - Har - Hay, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - He, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - Hi, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Ho, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - Hu - Hy, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - I, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - J, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - KA - KL, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - Ki - Ko, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - Kr - Ky, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - La, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - Le, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Li - Ly, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Mca - Mcd, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - Mce - Mck, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Mcl - Mcz, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Ma, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Me - Mi, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Mo - Mu, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Na - Ni, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - No - Ny, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - O, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File - Pa - Pe, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - Pi - Po, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr - Py, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr - Py, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr - Py, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr - Py, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - Pr - Py, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File - Q, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Alphabetic File - Ra - Re, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Alphabetic File - Ri - Rod, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Alphabetic File - Rog - Roz, 1923-1924 (Box 11 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Alphabetic File - Sa - Sca, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File - Sch - Scy, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File - Se - Sha, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File - She - Shy, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File - Si - Smi, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File - So - Sq, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File - Sta - Ste, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File - Sti - Sty, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File - Su - Sy, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File - Ta - Ti, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File - To - Tu, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File - To - Tu, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File - V, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - V, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Wa, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - We, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Wh, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - Wia - Wil, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Wim - Wiz, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Wo - Wy, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Y, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - Z, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File - American Association of Teachers Colleges, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - American Association of University Proffesors, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File - American Council of Education, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Applications Professional, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - George M. de Quesnel Bush, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File - Catalogs and Circulars, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File - Character Education - Printed, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File - Coal Contract, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - College Teachers of Education, 1923-1924 (Box 12 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Faculty Application, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Faculty Application, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Faculty Application, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Frank P. Graves Commissioner of Education, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Education, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Articles, Speeches, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Articles, Speeches, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic file - President's Committee of Fifty on College Hygiene, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic file - Prizes, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic file - Public Education, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic file - Speaking Engagements, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Speaking Engagement, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Speeches, Addresses, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Teachers' Agency Recommendation, 1923 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Trustees File, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Trustees File, 1923-1924 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1923-1939 (Box 13 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Commencement, 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Library Board, 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Publication- " What We Are Trying to Do", 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - State College- Public Education- Political, 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Summer School Teaching Positions- Acceptances, 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Summer Session, 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Summer Session- Budget, 1924 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - American Association of University Women, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Budget File, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Catalog Requests, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Catalog Requests, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Specifications, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - President's Report of One New York State College for Teachers, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Retirement System, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic Subject File- Speaking Engagement, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - State Teacher Association, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Trustees File, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Trustees File- President Bruhacher's notes, 1924-1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Association of Colleges and Preparatory Schools, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Board of Regents, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Chairs, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - College Entrance Board, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Commencement, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Education and Mental Adjustments, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Elementary School Teacher Training, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Faculty, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Field Service Fellowship, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Home Economics, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Letters Concerning Resident Hall, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Myskavia, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Publication "The needs of the state college for Teachers", 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Registration, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Speeches + Articles, 1925 (Box 14 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 35)
  - Brubacher- Kate Stonemen, 1925 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Teacher Conference, 1925 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Teacher Recruiting, 1925 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File Aa- Al, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File Am- AR, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File As- Ay, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File BAa- BAd, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File BAE- Bah, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File Bi- BL, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File BO, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File Bro- Bry, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File Bra- Bri, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File Bas- Baz, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File Bu- By, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File CA, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File Ce- Cl, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File CoA- CoN, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File CoO - CoZ, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File CR, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File Cu- Cy, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File DA- De, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File Di - Do, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File Dr - Dy, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File EA- EN, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)
  - Alphabetic File EO- Ey, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 25)
  - Alphabetic File FA- Fi, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 26)
  - Alphabetic File FL, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 27)
  - Alphabetic File Fr- Fy, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 28)
  - Alphabetic File Ga- Ge, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 29)
  - Alphabetic File Gi- Go, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 30)
  - Alphabetic File Gr- Gy, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 31)
  - Alphabetic File Haa- Han, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 32)
  - Alphabetic File Har- Hay, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 33)
  - Alphabetic File He, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 34)
  - Alphabetic File Hi- Hy, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 35)
  - Alphabetic File I, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 36)
  - Alphabetic File J, 1925-1926 (Box 15 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 37)
  - Alphabetic File Ka - Ke, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 1)
  - Alphabetic File Ki- Ky, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 2)
  - Alphabetic File LA, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 3)
  - Alphabetic File Le-Ly, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 4)
  - Alphabetic File McA- McZ, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 5)
  - Alphabetic File Ma- Mu, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 6)
  - Alphabetic File N-O, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 7)
  - Alphabetic File Pa-Po, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 8)
  - Alphabetic File Pr- Py, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 9)
  - Alphabetic File Q- Re, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 10)
  - Alphabetic File Ri- Rod, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 11)
  - Alphabetic File Rog- Ruz, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 12)
  - Alphabetic File SA- ScA, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 13)
  - Alphabetic File - Sch-Scy, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 14)
  - Alphabetic File - Se-Shp, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 15)
  - Alphabetic File - She-Shy, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 16)
  - Alphabetic File - Si-Smi, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 17)
  - Alphabetic File - So-Sq, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 18)
  - Alphabetic File - Stp-Ske, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 19)
  - Alphabetic File - Sti-Sty, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 20)
  - Alphabetic File - Su-Sy, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 21)
  - Alphabetic File - TA-Ti, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 22)
  - Alphabetic File, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 23)
  - Alphabetic File, 1925-1926 (Box 16 (2-Office of Abram Brubacher Records), Folder 24)